[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "Are you under the influence of any substances?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "P.T. Barnum.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "When you watch what's happening with Charlie right now, what are you thinking?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I think maybe the whole machete thing might have been something that he's running and gunning with right now but certainly the home tape that he did the night before, I fully recognized and I heard a clip that you had, I think it was Todd Bridges who made the comment of, yes, I've been there, I know that -- I know that guy.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Do you accept any of that?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't even think it's slowly right now.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "I mean are you seriously worried that Charlie Sheen is slowly killing himself here?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I mean I'm told --", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "I mean the man has an anger issue, a rage issue, and I think the more that people like you who have this incredible platform to come from who are -- I don't want to use the word enabling but who are sort of egging him on, tickling that little funny bone that says, yes, yes, this is -- hey, I've got, you know, Aunt Donna's DNA and I feel like people love to watch a circus, right?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Oh, without question.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "I mean when you hear him talk like that, what are you seeing, the classic signs of an addict in your view?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, look, he --", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "And being the face of CBS which is, you know, supposed to be a family, you know, network and the families out there, and he's working with a 9 or 10 or 11-year-old boy, so he comes into the set, he's off a crack run, he's been with a few hookers the night before, what do you think he's talking about with an 11-year-old?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I don't think I had ever been afraid of the drug itself before.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What was it that finally snapped you back into normal life again?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "And Mackenzie, for you, was it -- Mackenzie, for you, was it getting fired from the show that finally woke you up?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "I think it's got to be a combination of both.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Or does he have to save himself?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "It won't be easy for him as the doctor just mentioned.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "I mean if Charlie used to go down this road how difficult is it?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Am I right, Dr. Samuels?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "To be honest with you I couldn't answer that question.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Do you think he really has any concept of what's going on here?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "They were very nice people.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "What kind of people were your parents?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Absolutely none.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Was there any stress or trouble that you could look at and say well, maybe we should have seen warning signs here?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Probably 20 minutes after it had happened.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "When did you hear what had happened?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "It is just absolute disbelief.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What-- how do you possibly come to terms with it?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "No idea.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you know where he got the guns?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "You know, we will just continue to pull together like we had this last week and take care of one another.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "I mean, what do you think will happen next for this family?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "No, I never saw anything like this.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Did you get any kind of inkling that something like this could ever happen?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "That's a hard question for me to answer.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Do you think that is the correct way this should proceed?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Man, I don't know.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What can you possibly say to them?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Well, first, let me explain that as the ombudsman of NPR, I am not representing NPR.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Was she right to go?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, as I understand, the board basically decided that there have been too many things that have happened recently that would make it -- that hindered Vivian Schiller from actually going ahead and doing her job.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Can you be responsible if you are chief executive of such a huge organization for everything that everybody in it does and says?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Well, certainly not right off the bat.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Would it be easier if the NPR simply wasn't funded by the government?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, of course, it's fair game.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Is this kind of stunt fair game, do you think?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "No, but this is done all the time.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "This guy wouldn't have said this stuff if he knew he was being recorded, would he?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "No more so than Geraldo Rivera -- than Geraldo Rivera is.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Well, you are, really, aren't you?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "If James O'Keefe, who is an independent journalist, comes to me with something that doesn't sit right with me, I'm going to pass on it.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Where do you draw the line?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it's a cautionary tale, that this is a new world we live in.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "How do you ensure that somebody else isn't right now getting stitched up?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I will say this: the best coverage on this incident has been NPR.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Andrew?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I could accept that.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "They're not all choir boys, are they?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Because I woke up one day, 27 years old -- I remember it was my last court appearance.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "How did you manage to avoid the terrible fate that befell your colleagues?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Rock bottom for me was one day I was at a motel.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "What was rock bottom?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I was actually out at Lake San Antonio on my jet skis.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "When did you hear that Gary had died?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "That's exactly right.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "And takes care of you, yes.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Arnold, ain't I your big brother who loves you, who worries about you?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Well, for me, I know that addiction is very powerful.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Todd, when you see what's happened to Charlie Sheen, what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Because for me, I think what I was going through -- I call it cocaine psychosis.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Why do people do that?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Yeah, everyone -- anybody who is in addiction, you know what -- there's three things that can happen, end up mentally crazy the rest of your life, in prison the rest of your life or you're going to die.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Do you worry what will happen to Charlie if he doesn't get help?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I know him.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Have you met Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "A lot of things, but I would try to figure out the core of his problem.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "If you got a chance to talk to him, what would you say to him?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Certainly, yeah.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Do you think it was a mistake to get rid of Paula?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "110309pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "What do you think of Steven Tyler and J-Lo?", "qSentId": 727}]